const qBank = [
    {
      question:
        "Which premier league team has the record of 13 FA cup titles?",
      answers: ["Chelsea", "Liverpool", "Manchester united", "Arsenal"],
      correct: "Arsenal",
      questionId: "099099"
    },
    {
      question:
        'Who is the premier leagues all time goal scorer?',
      answers: ["Alan Shearer", "Frank Lampard", "Wayne Rooney", "Cristiano Ronaldo"],
      correct: "Alan Shearer",
      questionId: "183452"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following players have played both for Manchester City and Manchester United?",
      answers: ["David Silva", "Steven Gerrard", "Carlos Tevez", "Owen hargreeves"],
      correct: "Carlos Tevez",
      questionId: "267908"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Which one of the following players was not in the premier league team of the year in the season 2019/ 2020?",
      answers: [
        "Sergio Aguero",
        "Paul Pogba",
        "Harry Kane",
        "Sadio Mane"
      ],
      correct: "Harry Kane",
      questionId: "333247"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Which player kicked Manchester city's goal keeper Ederson in the face?",
      answers: ["Mo Salah", "Joey Barton", "Sadio Mane", "Marcus Rashford"],
      correct: "Sadio Mane",
      questionId: "496293"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which premier league side has the most premier league titles with 13 times?",
      answers: [
        "Manchester United",
        "Chelsea",
        "Liverpool",
        "Arsenal"
      ],
      correct: "Manchester United",
      questionId: "588909"
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which stadium has the least seats out of the following premier league grounds?',
      answers: ["Vitality Stadium", "Turf Moor", "Vicarage Road", "Selhurst Park"],
      correct: "Vitality Stadium",
      questionId: "648452"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Which premier league stadium has the most seating capacity?",
      answers: ["Old Trafford", "The Etihad", "Emirates", "The tottenham hotspur stadium"],
      correct: "Old Trafford",
      questionId: "786649"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who did man utd sign on the 31st January 2020 ?",
      answers: ["Odion Ighalo", "Slimani", "Bruno Fernandez", "Leo Messi"],
      correct: "Odion Ighalo",
      questionId: "839754"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which premier league player got the goal of the season in 2018/19 season?",
      answers: [
        "Troy Deeny",
        "Heung Min Son",
        "Andros Townsend",
        "Mo Salah"
      ],
      correct: "Andros Townsend",
      questionId: "98390"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who is Norwich manager?",
      answers: ["Eddie Howe", "Daniel Farke", "Emi Buendia", "Roy Hodgeson"],
      correct: "Daniel Farke",
      questionId: "1071006"
    },
    {
      question:
       "Who was bournemouths top premier league goalscorer in 2018/19?",
      answers: ["Joshua King", "Nathan Ake", "Callum Wilson", "Steve Cook"],
      correct: "Callum Wilson",
      questionId: "1174154"
    },
    {
      question:
       "3 players got the golden boot in the season of 2018/19 season, which of the following did not get the golden boot?",
      answers: ["Mo Salah", "Sadio Mane", "Aubameyang", "Sergio Aguero"],
      correct: "Sergio Aguero",
      questionId: "1226535"
    },
    {
      question:
       'Which premier league side where known as "The invincibles" in the 2003/04 season?',
      answers: ["Chelsea", "Manchester United", "Arsenal", "Liverpool"],
      correct: "Arsenal",
      questionId: "1310938"
    },
    {
      question:
       "Which team came 20th in the premier league 2017/18 season?",
      answers: ["Westbromwich albion", "Stoke city", "Southampton", "Cardif city"],
      correct: "Westbromwich albion",
      questionId: "1436873"
    },
    {
      question:
       "Which premier league side where known as the centurians when they hit a record of 100 points in the premier league?",
      answers: ["Manchester City", "Manchester United", "Arsenal", "Liverpool"],
      correct: "Manchester City",
      questionId: "1515110"
    },
    {
      question:
       "Who won the premier league player of the year in 2019?",
      answers: ["Mo salah", "Sergio Aguero", "Virgil Van Dijk", "Anthony Martial"],
      correct: "Virgil Van Dijk",
      questionId: "1642728"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who is Chelsea's record signing? ",
      answers: ["Eden Hazard", "Juan Mata", "Didier Drogba", "Kepa Arrizabalaga"],
      correct: "Kepa Arrizabalaga",
      questionId: "1747256"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who is Manchester United's record signing?",
      answers: ["Paul Pogba", "Harry Maguire", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "David Beckham"],
      correct: "Paul Pogba",
      questionId: "1822532"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who is the newcastle manager?",
      answers: [
        "Sean Dyce",
        "Steve Bruce",
        "Tammy Abraham",
        "Nigel Pearson"
      ],
      correct: "Steve Bruce",
      questionId: "195075"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who scored a hatrick on  City's first game of the 2019/20 season against Westham?",
      answers: ["Sergio Aguero", "Raheem Sterling", "Gabriel Jesus", "Kevin De Bruyne"],
      correct: "Raheem Sterling",
      questionId: "2019778"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "In what season did leads last play in the premier league?",
      answers: ["2016/17", "2005/06", "2003/04", "2007/08"],
      correct: "2003/04",
      questionId: "2134343"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who has the most premier league assists of all time?",
      answers: [
        "Ryan Giggs",
        "Kevin De Bruyne",
        "Wayne Rooney",
        "Jack Grealish"
      ],
      correct: "Ryan Giggs",
      questionId: "2210799"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who has made the most premier league tackles of all time?",
      answers: ["Virgil van dijk", "Wilfred Ndidi", "Gareth Barry", "Mark noble"],
      correct: "Gareth Barry",
      questionId: "2379831"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who has the most saves in the premier league of all time?",
      answers: ["Edwin Van Der Sar", "Ben Foster", "Petr Cech", "David De Gea"],
      correct: "Ben Foster",
      questionId: "2426418"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Which player has been unlucky enough to strike the woodwork 44 times?",
      answers: ["Robin Van Persie", "Wayne Rooney", "Phil Jones", "Steven Gerrard"],
      correct: "Robin Van Persie",
      questionId: "2510086"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who has won the most premier league player of the month awards at 7?",
      answers: [
        "Heung Min Son",
        "Sergio Aguero",
        "Mo salah",
        "Paul pogba"
      ],
      correct: "Sergio Aguero",
      questionId: "2685745"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which premier league player has picked up a record of 123 yellow cards in his career?",
      answers: ["Paul Scholes", "Frank Lampard", "Gareth Barry", "Mustafi"],
      correct: "Gareth Barry",
      questionId: "2796884"
    },
    {
      question: 
      "Who won the premier league in 2015/16 season?",
      answers: ["Leicester city", "Manchester City", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
      correct: "Leicester city",
      questionId: "2838900"
    },
    {
      question: "Which premier league team scored the most goals in the 2018/19 season?",
      answers: ["Manchester city", "Manchester United", " Liverpool", "Wolves"],
      correct: "Manchester city",
      questionId: "298060"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the heighest paid player in the premier league?",
      answers: ["Alexis Sanchez", "Paul Pogba", "Sergio Aguero", "Virgil Van Dijk"],
      correct: "Alexis Sanchez",
      questionId: "3096579"
    },
    {
      question: "Huddersfield town had an awful 2018/19 season, how many points did they get after 38 games?",
      answers: [
        "11",
        "14",
        "16",
        "22"
      ],
      correct: "16",
      questionId: "3182461"
    },
    {
      question: "Who were the 1999 treble winners?",
      answers: [
        "Leeds Unitd",
        "Manchester United",
        "Arsenal",
        "Liverpool"
      ],
      correct: "Manchester United",
      questionId: "3239112"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following teams have never been relegated from the premier league?",
      answers: ["Leicester city", "Everton", "Manchester city", "Burnley"],
      correct: "Everton",
      questionId: "3318503"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which keeper saved 2 penalties against Manchester united in the season 2019/20?",
      answers: ["Nic Pope", "Tim Krul", "Alisson Becker", "Kepa"],
      correct: "Tim Krul",
      questionId: "3410327"
    },
    {
      question: "What national team does Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang play for",
      answers: ["France", "Nigeria", "Gabon", "Chad"],
      correct: "Gabon",
      questionId: "3542596"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has scored the most own goals in premier league history?",
      answers: ["Phil Jones", "Dennis Erwin", "Rio Ferdinand", "Richard Dunne"],
      correct: "Richard Dunne",
      questionId: "3667517"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has had the most offsides in premier league history?",
      answers: [
        "Berbatov",
        "Adebayor",
        "Benteke",
        "Aguero"
      ],
      correct: "Adebayor",
      questionId: "3791672"
    },
    {
      question: "In the season of 2018/19 how many players played every minute of every game?",
      answers: ["10", "0", "5", "12"],
      correct: "12",
      questionId: "3893585"
    },
    {
      question: "Who got the most assists in 2018/19 season?",
      answers: ["Kevin De Bruyne", "Eden Hazard", "Juan Mata", "Willian"],
      correct: "Eden Hazard",
      questionId: "3913430"
    },
    {
      question: "Which keeper had the most clean sheets in the 2018/19 season?",
      answers: ["Alisson", "Ederson", "Kepa", "De Gea"],
      correct: "Alisson",
      questionId: "4049121"
    },
    
  ];
  
  export default (n = 10) =>
    Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
  